Norhan Mostafa

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Creative and detail-oriented graphic designer with exceptional skill level and experience in various mediums, such as vector art, motion graphics, and illustrations. Highly adept with programs in Adobe Suite, such as InDesign, Photoshop, After Effects, Adobe XD and Illustrator.

ABOUT ME

Creative and hardworking professional with 10 years' dedicated experience in graphic designing industry.

Working knowledge of design principles, practices, and methods of digital art, production procedures, printing system, and industry terminologies.

I also have experience with motion graphics design from my previous work as a graphic designer. I have also used motion graphics in my personal projects. In addition, I have taken several courses on motion graphics and animation.

LENGUAGES

ARABIC

ENGLISH

JAPANESE

CONTACT INFO



+01061392895



norhan.mostafa83@gmail.com



Schutz., Alexandria. Egypt



norhanmostafam

Вē

behance.net/norhanmostafaM



WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Graphic Designer

Media Solutions UAE - Alexandria branch

Feb, 2024- Present

Flowtechtics

Dec, 2022 - Jan, 2024

El Alamein for Packaging Industry

Sep, 2021 - Dec, 2022

Interface Agency - Marketing Agency

Nov, 2020 - Sep, 2021

Junior Graphic Designer

Four Corners Group

Mar, 2017 - July, 2019 (Freelancer)

Viola TV | Animation Studio

Jun. 2014 - Mar. 2017



EDUCATION

DESIGN GUIDE 2021-2022

Certificate of completion in prepress management & Color Separation

GRAPHITOPIA 2016-2017

Certificate of completion in Motion Graphics

AASTMT 2014-2015

Mini Certificate In 2D Graphic design for print & Web design

ALEXANDRIA UNIVERSITY 2009-2014

BA Degree Of fine arts, Graphic design



SKILLS



SOFTWARE

- Multitasking
- Flexibility
- Layout
- Communication
- Composition
- Typography

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe Acrobat

